Hi, welcome back.
We're doing Chants of Cenar.
And we're on a new floor.
Let's see this thing here.
Seaking you are.
Found we have.
Oh, there's something down there though.
Some writing.
So this guy is seeking something.
And these guys have found it.
Let's move it.
Direct translation here.
We got some new symbols.
Oh, very interesting stuff here.
Right off the bat I'm noticing some similarities here.
We got straight lines.
That has to be a group of similar words.
Then we have circular ones.
Yeah, also notice how these straight lines have lines connecting at the bottom.
That has to mean something specific.
Because this one has a line connecting at the top.
Then again, this one has sort of in the middle.
Okay, I'm not sure about that.
I have a lot of these so far and I have no idea what any of them mean.
Hold on a minute.
I want to go back to... Oh, actually, you know what?
Okay, so the game expects me to already know this.
Wait a sec.
This has to mean direct translation, right?
Meaning this is that.
And this is that.
It has to mean that.
So you are seeking... I'm just going to assume it's in the correct order here and I say correct, but you know what I mean.
In non Yoda speak, meaning you are seeking.
So this guy is you and the circular one is are or is.
And this guy right up here, or is it this one is seeking or seek.
Okay, what about the bottom one?
We have found.
We.
Have.
Oh, wait a minute.
Does that make sense?
To have is not the same as to be.
Seeking you are.
But wait a minute.
This is a plural.
So he's speaking to a bunch of people here like y'all y'all are seeking, you know.
So maybe let me think.
Yeah, this is we.
Actually found we have is not even in here.
It's just saying we found.
And this is saying you seek or y'all seek.
So now I'm thinking maybe the circular one is plural.
But if that is plural.
Oh, wait a minute now.
Maybe they're going in complete reverse in this floor.
Oh, God, I don't know.
Okay, so we have one for plural, right?
There is a plural here somewhere.
I'm assuming it's the circle one.
Yeah.
Let's put that in.
Let's just rename this plural.
So that would mean also this one needs to be designated.
So we find or we found this meaning.
But wait a minute.
If that is plural, then this would mean this is we or us.
Oh, God.
What if plural comes after in this language?
You know, if this guy is after this, it could mean.
We, in this case, that's how they pluralize things.
So this is actually me.
Me.
Whoops.
You.
Yeah, I think so.
Let's put this for me.
And you would have to be that one.
Plural, I think, is this one.
Find.
Is.
Wait, did I even designate that yet?
I didn't.
This has to be find.
And this one is seek slash want.
I freaking nailed that.
Okay, nice.
I did metagame it a little bit because the earlier floor played with the order of, you know, the entire sentence.
And I just thought it would make sense for them to try and mess with me this way.
You seek, we found.
I mean, yeah, yeah.
Yep, that's exactly how that works.
Amazing.
Okay, we got a good start here, then.
What about these?
Let's go back to where we found those because I had zero clue about those.
Here.
So this is clearly an elevator.
And these are the controls for the elevator.
Well, can I?
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
No power, it seems.
Oh, can I walk up there through this beam?
Okay, I don't think so.
Let me play with this again.
This could mean on.
What could that mean?
So we're dealing with an elevator.
And this seems like a power box, right?
We have four buttons.
Not sure what this is.
There's also these lights up here.
Let me see again.
Okay, that's telling me I did it wrong.
That's not correct.
Okay.
I have to do it in the right order.
No, what about this one?
And then aha.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Oh,
they're numbers.
Genius.
That's so smart.
I was wondering about numbers in this game, but apparently they are dealing with it now.
Shit, what did I do?
So this one was first.
Second.
Oh, God.
Wait, wait.
This one is one.
Oh, God.
I wish there was an easier way to do this.
This one is two with the two lines there.
That makes sense, I guess.
Two.
The triangular one is three, which makes sense, actually.
Whoops.
Triangle is three.
Makes a lot of sense.
And four was this one.
Half circle.
Okay.
And then we have this one is five.
The filled circle.
Okay, so we should be able to do this now.
One, two, three, four, five.
Very nice.
Yep.
Straight up just numbers.
Cool.
Okay, cool.
And now we have power?
Yeah.
All right.
I got to remind myself, actually... Did I come from here?
I did.
Okay.
And what was down here?
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Wait, actually... What was back here?
Yeah, okay.
Just double-checking here.
Just want to make absolutely sure that I don't miss anything.
Is there anything else in there?
Okay.
Let me interact with this one again.
Maybe I can actually translate something now.
TIE Fighter.
Okay, there's nothing here.
There's no connection.
I also want to go back to the first floor again, because apparently the Warriors opened the gate, right?
And there's also a door there that I want to explore.
The door that we couldn't access very early on.
I want to go check that out.
See if there's any connection there.
Let's go up.
Oh!
Very mechanical and factory-like area.
I'm liking this aesthetic.
So I can go up, I guess.
Oh, nice.
I like the sounds on the stairs.
Simple stuff like that makes me so happy, you know?
What's this?
It's like a flowchart of sorts.
This has a star on it.
It says no.
Oh, what the hell is going on here?
Oh, wait, is this a map?
Stairs?
Is this where I am?
Is that why the star is there?
Number one?
Number two?
Oh my god.
Holy cannoli!
Calm yourself with the new glyphs?
That's crazy.
Wait a second.
So this one is find, seek, want, verbs, right?
This is a verb.
This one is a verb.
It's like this circle thing with the little circle at the end.
That's a verb.
What about others?
This one is me.
You.
So a straight line with something happening in the center.
Do we have any other thing like that here?
Nope, we don't.
But we do have a bunch of triangles here.
I wonder if those are adjectives or nouns or something else like that.
Weird looking language, but cool.
Plural.
Verb.
Yeah, I don't know what any of that means.
No clue.
Oh, yo, we go talk to them.
Sup?
Wow, he actually said hello.
Me?
Scientist?
I am, or maybe he's telling me his name, but that doesn't make sense, right?
They wouldn't have a glyph for a name.
Me, something, you.
And that's a verb.
That makes sense, right?
We know this is a verb.
Me greet you.
Greet.
Greetings.
To greet someone.
Oh, this music is great.
I'm a scientist.
My greetings to you, right?
What about the other guy?
Okay, I guess he's not saying anything.
You're not going to question how I get up here?
Why is nobody questioning my methods?
There's an elevator here.
I want to try not to get lost for once in a new area.
Let's really try not to get lost.
So I came up here.
There's an elevator going up.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The flowchart, it is a map.
That's an elevator.
Yeah, stairs on the left.
Ah, but wait, we can't, no, no, we are here now.
And we go up with an elevator to here.
Second floor, that makes sense.
First floor, second floor.
Right, stairs leading up and down.
So if I go right on this floor, we're going to get to this place, which is something.
And if we go left, we go over here to these two rooms.
Let's try and see what these two rooms are first.
That is a map.
Incredible.
Yes, wait.
No monsters allowed?
Is that what that means?
There's a console here.
Now, I was expecting there to be a room south of here as well.
There's a room north and there should be a room south, according to the map we just saw.
Wait a minute, I'm going to go back once more real quick.
Just to see this again.
Yeah, that's the same thing I saw north.
So there is something to the south.
Maybe it's connected further down the line.
It's like this triangle with an arrow and two dots.
Okay, let's see if I remember that when we get to it.
Nice aesthetic here.
I really like this.
Oh, we need an access card.
I don't have it.
They're like a highly technical civilization or culture.
Technologically advanced.
That's just a lever.
Oh.
Train passing through?
Or a mine cart, I mean.
What?
What was the point of that?
Do I have to put something in this wagon at some point?
Oh, here it is.
Yeah, this is the room south.
All right.
There's a way here as well.
Let's try going north first.
Yeah, that leads us to the stairs we saw on the map.
Makes sense.
Okay, go back, go back.
Let's try going down.
So what does that mean?
We have to pay attention to what is inside of here.
Oh, but I can't enter.
Okay.
So both of the rooms here require an access card.
Gotcha.
Let's try and take the stairs.
Which is going to take us to the second floor, of course.
I'm really trying to keep the map we saw in my mind so I don't get lost.
Get up here.
Look at all the pipes.
Library?
Look at them studying.
Is this some
kind of machine with a lever on it?
This means four, three, two... What?
One.
There's a pipe attached to it.
Maybe this means water because it goes in a pipe or oil, some kind of liquid.
No, no, this is a verb.
Verb.
Could it be flow?
The flow.
I'm actually going to write flow.
Whoops.
I want it to be flow so bad.
I don't know what we're looking at though.
Oh, is this a coffee machine?
Look.
Coffee beans in, water in.
You press the button to, I don't know, do something and then you get the water out or get the coffee.
So you pull this up until this is over on this spot.
On the meter.
Plans for a coffee machine?
I don't know.
Let's talk to this dude.
Hello.
You seek... something.
So that's a noun, I guess.
Because I can't be seeking a verb.
Actually, that's not true.
I could seek to ascend, right?
Let's remove that.
You seek slash want.
What do I seek slash want?
Knowledge?
A book?
Are you looking for a book?
He's a librarian?
Maybe book?
Knowledge?
I mean, it could be anything here, but...
Oh, wait, is he asking?
You wouldn't just say you seek book.
It would have to be a question, right?
But maybe the question part of this language is just sort of baked in.
There's no specific symbol for it.
Yeah, this is most likely just a question.
What's that?
A ring?
Number one.
What?
The one ring?
This is so intriguing.
So, one, this.
These are all triangles, by the way.
Maybe they are trying to get rid of the demon problem via the scientific method.
Maybe they have some plans to get rid of them, or maybe even help them.
Maybe they're trying to turn them into, I don't know, non-evil creatures.
That would be the scientific way, right?
The warrior ways to kill them.
What's that?
Oh, look at the coins!
They have the shape of the zoom meetings.
The zoom terminals.
Also has the shape of the devotee a little bit.
That looks like a devotee hat.
Two.
Ring?
Coin?
I am so confused.
I
can go that way.
There's a big library.
Let me see this one again.
We have to insert... Oh, insert coin?
To operate the machine.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What was the word for coin?
I don't think we had a word for coin.
It was just a number, wasn't it?
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Here we go, here we go.
One is that one.
Oh, I get it, I get it.
I'm so stupid.
This is ring.
Triangle with circle this one.
That's ring, of course.
And the next one is coin.
Coin?
Right.
Okay, okay, okay, good, good, good.
Insert ring or coin?
What is the third one?
What are you saying again?
You seek.
Maybe he's asking if I want coffee.
You know, hey, you want coffee?
Go find a coin first.
Slot it into the machine and follow the instructions.
Oh, there's also something here.
Oh,
that's a fire thingy you can make fire with.
What's the word for that?
You know what I mean.
Yeah, that is a lighter.
It's a lighter.
I think.
Is it?
That's fire.
And that is definitely the thing that strikes with friction, right?
There's two words here.
There's an arrow pointing there.
Fire maker?
Fire creator?
Oh, wait, that's a verb.
Verb.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, this has to mean create fire.
Watch me be right on this.
Fire.
Create slash make.
Yeah, yep.
Do I know what he's saying now?
No, right, of course not, because that was book and knowledge.
Let's try going through the door up here on the right.
That is going to take us.
So right now we are in the second floor to the left.
Now we're going to go towards the center, I think.
Book knowledge.
I think I was right on that.
That's book.
It's not knowledge.
Because it's multiple books.
It's just books.
Where's that?
Simple.
I'm losing my mind.
It's just book.
We got it.
Okay.
Now this is going to take us to the elevator, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that's the same elevator we saw.
This is the elevator here.
Nice that we have another map.
Ah, but wait a second now.
Was I here just now or here?
Yeah, look, now the star is here.
Maybe this one means out of order or broken.
Because the elevator doesn't work.
Looks like someone put a sticky note on it, right?
That could mean broken.
Broken.
Put a star on that just to indicate that we're not very sure about it.
I need to go back here and see which one of these was library.
Because for sure that means library, one of those symbols.
Ah, wait a sec though.
So I came from there, which means this is now north and that is south.
Ooh, look at that.
Another mysterious door.
Yeah, does it need the exact same symbol?
Let's try to remember.
It's like a line with two L's on each side.
Okay.
Let's remember that the mysterious door on this level is located here.
Directly south of the library.
Actually not quite directly south.
Southwest.
But south, because this door is inaccessible, so we're just going to call it south.
What's up here?
Whoa.
What the hell is that?
Oh, look at all these little pieces down here.
Can I not pick them up or put them in somehow?
Almost looks like someone broke it on purpose.
Ooh, look at all this machinery.
Verb.
What's this?
Coin, ring.
The coin power is only at one out of three.
Same with the ring, but the other ones are full power, whatever that means.
Let's see that one.
Oh, these are different weights.
Do we have to balance a weight here?
Red, red and green because they didn't have full power.
Oh, wait a second.
Is this the machine?
Is this the machine they're talking about?
Let's see that one.
Here's where the coffee comes out.
Maybe
this means dispense.
Why is there an X there?
Oh, okay, just to cancel something, maybe?
Oh, the X is on the door as well.
It's to open the door, I guess.
Wait a second now.
Okay.
Very satisfying sounds when you click on them.
I have no clue, bro.
I have no idea what's happening here.
Oh, oh, I can click on these.
I need to deposit more coins and rings, I guess.
Let's head down here.
Okay, so now we are back at the second floor elevator.
Hopefully there's no nuclear waste in those barrels down there.
Okay, so what is this guy doing over here?
Hello.
Me find...
something.
Me seek want something.
Look at the similarity of these two glyphs here.
Could it be me seek barrel?
No, wait, me find...
I found barrel, but I was looking for something else.
Yeah, I have no clue what that means.
What is he doing?
He's counting.
One, two, three.
There's three blue.
Oh, wait, is he talking about colors?
One, two, three blue barrels.
Hold on a minute.
I'm looking for...
green, maybe?
What I found blue?
No, that doesn't make any sense.
Actually, you wouldn't say that.
But it wouldn't surprise me if they somehow incorporate colors into the language as well at some point.
Let's go down here.
Watch down this way.
Oh, a gathering!
Cafeteria.
That's cafeteria.
Maybe cocktail bar.
Look at the way this is shaped like a cocktail.
I'm just going to call it cafeteria, though.
Cafeteria.
Or like dining hall, you know?
Mess hall.
The eatery.
Oh, look at this up here!
Oh, lololololo!
Would you look at that?
One, two, three.
Eating time!
Five, six, seven.
Nine, ten, eleven.
Eating time.
That is amazing.
Yeah, it's not time yet.
Wait, is it actually going?
Oh, time is moving, look!
The second hand is moving.
So this means six.
Oh my god, that's so smart.
And you know what?
Why didn't I think about this?
Of course this is a number!
Because these look exactly like these.
Obviously.
What the hell am I doing?
Six!
And that's, uh...
So hold on.
No, wait.
Seven, I mean.
This is six.
Seven is the weirdo there.
Seven.
This one is... let's see.
After eating, so seven, eight, nine.
Right, that's the same one.
This is nine.
One, two, three.
Four, five.
We don't have any others, do we?
Okay.
Very cool.
Uh, I wonder when, uh, when this reaches eat, are they all gonna eat?
I wanna eat too!
Eat, eat, eat, eat.
Also, I wanna talk to you.
Greetings.
Cafeteria broken?
Oh!
Closed!
It's closed!
That would also make sense with the elevator being closed.
For maintenance, maybe.
Cafeteria opens at four!
Yes!
Yeah!
And you know what else makes sense?
Look at this.
It's a triangle pointing down, meaning close.
We got the triangle pointing up means open.
Smart.
Ha ha!
I fucking love this game.
It makes me feel like a genius when I figure this out, you know?
And that's always good in a video game.
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta go back here.
It's not fourth just yet.
Kinda wanna just wait for four.
Maybe we can go explore a couple other things while we wait.
Oh yeah, this guy!
Excuse me!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
You want nine?
Oh, so you're missing a couple, huh?
I see.
How come we didn't get any new pages we can fill out, by the way?
Isn't that kinda crazy?
We should've gotten a lot of pages at this point.
Or maybe not, I don't know.
Uh, was there anything else down here?
So we had the door?
There wasn't anything else, right?
No, okay.
Let's quickly take the elevator.
That's just a nice shortcut.
Yep.
Precisely.
Just had to check that.
Let's go back up.
I wanna go to the cafeteria at four.
I'm so hungry.
I wonder what they're serving up here.
Hopefully some pasta or something.
Maybe a nice salad on the side.
Oh, it's almost time.
Here we go, here we go.
Nothing like a good meal after a hard day of science, right?
I am a scientist, too.
Can I enter?
I require sustenance.
Here we go.
Yep.
Yes, I'm coming, too.
Yeah, dude.
Cafeteria is open.
Damn right it is.
Oh, that looks like a weird slop you're being served there.
Just different colored soups.
What is that?
That guy fell asleep at his table.
Apiocco.
I got some silverware.
Ah, would you look at... what?
That doesn't make any sense.
Unless... it doesn't mean coin, maybe it means silver.
Silverware?
Okay.
I'm...
Okay, I'm a little bit confused by that, actually.
Which one was that?
Uh, this one?
Slash silver?
I don't know.
He's snoring.
Okay, go this way.
Can I... can I deposit silver here?
No?
Really?
Oh, it's this one.
What?
No way.
Okay.
Maybe I have to smelt it down?
First, into like a bar.
By the way, because look...
Look at the shapes of these openings.
That's totally the shape of a... of a bar or an ingot.
Right?
They need... these are raw materials, I think.
Ah, that's totally what it is.
Let's go back to the library.
I need to see something.
I need to see what the... what the ring was made of.
Probably gold.
Let's see that one.
Yeah, look there is silvery.
Silvery.
Yeah, just keep it as coin slash silver for now.
That's okay.
This one...
Yeah, look at it.
It's so gold.
Which one was that?
Ring.
Actually, I'm gonna put gold and ring F.
I'm pretty sure it's gold, honestly.
Ah, but I am... I'm gonna write it anyway.
Because, who knows?
Maybe I'm wrong.
Gold, ah, ring.
Just be on the safe side here.
Man, I wonder when we're gonna get more pages to fill out.
I love filling out the book and confirming everything.
It gives me that same sort of dopamine hit that Return of the Obra didn't gave me.
So that's where I came from.
Did I ever walk up these stairs?
Oh!
Oh, shit.
Okay, there's more.
Okay, scientists and...
um, bards.
Scientists.
Bards.
Bard.
Powers.
Something.
So...
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I'm pretty sure this doesn't mean bard.
I'm pretty sure that means artist.
Artists and scientists...
produce things that power...
I don't know, civilization?
A group together?
Scientists and...
artists together...
are called what?
I don't know.
Community?
Hold on.
I'm gonna call this...
I'm so sure about this, by the way.
Because there's no way these people would call them bards as well, right?
Maybe musicians.
But they're definitely into the whole art stuff, right?
These guys are into the whole science.
Yeah, I don't know what that could mean.
Hmm.
Yeah, I don't know.
What could it mean?
Scientists and artists...
as a group?
What are they called?
What is that called?
Students?
Students of art and science?
No.
I don't know.
Let's call it artist...
or scientist plus artist for now.
I'm not sure what that could be.
Okay.
Very weird.
Is that the same one we saw downstairs here?
Yes.
So the triangular one is three, and then this is four.
Got the weird sort of situation there.
Are they gonna have more things on display up here?
Ooh, a mural!
And would you look at that!
That is indeed a zoom terminal.
I have become infatuated with the zoom terminals, by the way.
Oh my god, what is this?
Who are they?
Someone creates...
the sun?
Or... God?
Door?
Communication?
Um...
Wait, they have wings!
Angels and God...
stay away to heaven?
Knocking on God's door?
They are wearing or holding wands.
As if...
I don't know, magicians?
Um...
Let's see here.
The fact that this one did not get revealed right now over here...
means I've seen it before.
But where?
I don't recall where I saw this.
Let's just write, uh...
angel slash...
magician.
And the last one could be...
What are they making right now?
Zoom terminals.
They made the zoom terminals, whoever these people are.
Uh... where's that one?
Zoom terminal.
I don't know what else to call it at this point.
Neat image though.
Hmm...
That would have been a nice idea for a YouTube thumbnail though.
This right here.
Very cool.
Oooh, let's see this.
Book, we know that one.
These two together, man, what is that called?
Well, I don't know, but I know what the word is for it.
It's scientist plus artist.
Right?
Uh...
Could just be civilization.
Or humans.
Could be humans, actually.
They're all men, right?
They're all part of humanity.
This up here we also kinda know.
This is, uh, let's see here.
Angel magician...
makes...
that.
Zoom terminals.
I can't wait to see what these actually mean.
Okay, let's take a look.
Are you kidding me?
It's actually just a door?
Okay, I guess that makes sense.
Fine.
I mean, I was close enough.
I would say an angel magician is kind of a fairy, right?
Book, of course.
Alchemist?
Oh, that makes sense.
Gold, silver.
All the elements?
That actually makes a lot of sense.
God damn it!
I thought I was so smart when I called this artist.
I was metagaming a little bit, you know?
Thinking, oh, the other people called themselves bards.
Surely these people are not gonna call them bards.
Damn it!
Okay, well, that's fine.
Brother?
I'm sorry, that makes no sense.
How could anyone deduce that?
Huh?
Are they related?
Like, in a family, do they share the same mother?
I don't get it.
But I guess, you know, whatever.
I was right with the idea behind that glyph, just not the exact meaning.
Okay.
Then again, one of the bards on the bard floor did call me brother, right?
Yeah, it's confusing because there were also these two bards that were being all jolly together, you know?
Drinking and holding arms, being like, we are brothers.
And that would look like they were brothers, right?
But this doesn't smell of that.
Okay.
We are closer to the truth here.
Oh, we can talk to this dude.
Ooh, you say a lot.
Oh.
I found a book about bards.
You did?
Can I see it?
No, apparently not.
Ooh, let's see this one.
Which element is it?
Copper.
Maybe.
Even though...
Hold on a minute.
Three.
What's the one with the thing going up and to the right?
That one.
Copper?
I don't know.
Could be.
Where's the last one?
Maybe I'm not going to get that answered here.
I can go this way, though.
Ooh, a hat!
Ah, look at that.
I'm not sure what this is.
I don't know.
Some element.
I forgot the symbol for the last one as well.
We're going to have to review that.
Hold on, let's go back and just... Oh!
Ah!
Okay, but hold on a sec, hold on a sec.
Let me just quickly confirm.
On the chart over here.
Gold slash ring.
Okay, that one with the ch-ch on it.
Got it.
Back in.
Now, it's just a matter of...
of excluding here now.
So...
This one is this one.
Whatever it is, I'm not sure what it is.
This one is that one.
Then we have gold.
And we have silver.
Gold, silver, copper, carbon.
Okay.
It looked like carbon at first when I saw it at a distance, but then when I saw it up close, it had this sort of green hue, which confused me.
I would have put in carbon otherwise, I kid you not.
Like, look at this right now.
That looks like a piece of carbon, right?
But when you look up close, it's green.
That confused me a little bit.
But okay.
Ah, right.
We got some writing here.
All right.
What is this saying?
Actually, I can't focus with this thing going fling.
Pick it up.
Oh.
There's a little note in here.
What?
Okay, that I don't understand.
Why is he hiding something in his hat?
Let's see the drawing again.
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
This is circled.
So, wait a minute.
Triangle means three, five, seven.
Or nine, I mean.
Nine, three, five.
And why am I saying that?
Because look at the symbols here.
This is five.
Combined with that is three.
Then we have nine.
Oh, is it adding things together?
Is that what's happening?
Seventeen, maybe?
And what's... So, hold on a minute.
Here's there's three lines going across.
Relation to this, maybe?
Seventeen.
Wait a minute.
So, five is on the left.
Three is on the left.
But nine is on the right.
Maybe this is how they do math.
Maybe this is adding, this is subtracting?
I don't know.
This would be minus one in that case.
What the hell?
And this... I don't know what that means.
Let's see this drawing again.
So, what is he saying here?
He's saying that...
Pointing down...
Two lines across.
Carbon and...
Silver.
I mean, alchemists, they're combining elements, right?
It's what they're doing.
And here he's saying carbon plus...
Is that gold?
Yeah.
Carbon plus gold creates...
uh...
How much is that?
That is... nine?
No, sorry, five?
Oh, that one is copper.
What does this mean?
Oh, this is also math.
So, we have three and...
one?
Yeah.
Four.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I see.
So, here we have three in total.
There's a little thing on the left there.
What does that mean?
Could be you?
No.
Maybe he's saying you need this much gold and this much copper creates...
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, this much gold...
creates this much copper.
If you do something, I don't know.
Triangle...
Okay, I'm not sure about that, actually.
Am I going to note this down in my book?
That being noticed anywhere?
It's not... Okay, so presumably that means it's not terribly important?
I'm not sure.
But why would he be hiding something in his hat?
I have no idea what this means.
Like, the metagamer in me wants to say this means math.
But why would anyone just write math in their hat?
That doesn't make any sense.
Right?
Yeah, that doesn't make any sense.
Uh... Oh, maybe that means... formula or something.
Yeah, I don't know.
I honestly have no clue.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to write...
Because I don't know what to put in here, I'm just going to put...
found in hat.
And I'm going to do something like this to signify that it's not a guess, it's just where I found it.
So why is it doing that funny...
Look, when I hold my mouse here, that's a bug.
That's weird.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to take a break here.
Thanks for watching.
I'll see you in the next one.
Bye-bye.